[{"Answer_text": "Students will gain a deeper understanding of calculating area since they discover the nature of the formula by themselves. However, I have to say I am a bit skeptical about guided discovery because I think there is a possibility that students may only remember the formula they \"invent\" rather than the most effective one.", "Question_id": 5, "Student_score_on_question": 0.75, "Student_choice_on_question": "A,B,C", "Quiz_score": 6.5, "Average_quizzes_score": 7.7}, {"Answer_text": "Students are likely to gain the ability to conditionalize the concept, or better understand how it applies or changes according to the scenario in a more refined way. The contrasting cases will mean that student's attention is focused on important features. Because they are participating in invent-then-tell, the students will retain the concept longer as well.", "Question_id": 5, "Student_score_on_question": 0.75, "Student_choice_on_question": "A,B,C", "Quiz_score": 9.75, "Average_quizzes_score": 8.1}, {"Answer_text": "They should have a better conceptual understanding and remember it longer compared to a strictly lecture and practice method. They will also do better on transfer tasks.", "Question_id": 5, "Student_score_on_question": 0.75, "Student_choice_on_question": "A,B,C", "Quiz_score": 8.25, "Average_quizzes_score": 7.2}, {"Answer_text": "by following the 'contrasting' path, students will develop a better understanding of the problem and hence will perceive a better learning of the surface area concept (i.e. will be able to come up with a formula for the surface of a proper pentagon). They are also likely to remember the formulas longer as the concept they understood will allow them to basically write down the formula without memorising it by heart, so they fill not forget the formulas. As for other options, the performance on unrelated math concepts is questionable and there is no evidence that it happens. As for the remaining option, 'better' here needs to be clarified. Better than if they didn't participate in this activity? If so, then It is not clear. If instead of this activity, students were doing standard test and practise, then their performance on the test (that happens right after the education) might be the same, because they remember well what formula applies to what figure.", "Question_id": 5, "Student_score_on_question": 0.5, "Student_choice_on_question": "B,C", "Quiz_score": 9.5, "Average_quizzes_score": 8.1}, {"Answer_text": "This is a formula application problem, so guided discovery do not have benefits over formula application type of task. However, it helps with the delayed transfer and the contextualizing.", "Question_id": 5, "Student_score_on_question": 0.5, "Student_choice_on_question": "B,C", "Quiz_score": 8.0, "Average_quizzes_score": 7.6}, {"Answer_text": "Students will remember these formulae for a long period of time as compared to the just listening to lectures. They will be able to transfer this learning to their final exams as well and not only tests taken after the lesson. Students will also better select right formula for the problem as they know which formula applies for which shape.", "Question_id": 5, "Student_score_on_question": 1.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "A,C", "Quiz_score": 8.25, "Average_quizzes_score": 6.4}, {"Answer_text": "increased attention Generate their own knowledge Summarizing", "Question_id": 5, "Student_score_on_question": 1.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "A,C", "Quiz_score": 8.75, "Average_quizzes_score": 7.8}, {"Answer_text": "I think only C because the research does not support ICC yields better performance on surface concepts or performance on the task, but it does support that it yields a better result of transfer to another scenario, yet in the problem it say \"unrelated math concepts\" I feel that is not too rigorous and not proved.", "Question_id": 5, "Student_score_on_question": 0.75, "Student_choice_on_question": "C", "Quiz_score": 7.5, "Average_quizzes_score": 7.7}, {"Answer_text": "See the deeper structure of problems", "Question_id": 5, "Student_score_on_question": 1.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "A,C", "Quiz_score": 7.5, "Average_quizzes_score": 7.6}, {"Answer_text": "Students will remember the formulas longer than they would with lecture-practice method. Students will be better at telling the formula of triangle and that of rectangle apart.", "Question_id": 5, "Student_score_on_question": 0.75, "Student_choice_on_question": "A,B,C", "Quiz_score": 7.25, "Average_quizzes_score": 6.8}, {"Answer_text": "invented solutions can help students understand", "Question_id": 5, "Student_score_on_question": 0.25, "Student_choice_on_question": "B", "Quiz_score": 7.25, "Average_quizzes_score": 6.9}, {"Answer_text": "Students will have a deeper understanding of the concept of area in general. They will be better at calculate areas in transfer tasks, even after a period of delay.", "Question_id": 5, "Student_score_on_question": 0.25, "Student_choice_on_question": "B", "Quiz_score": 6.75, "Average_quizzes_score": 7.3}, {"Answer_text": "Students are more likely to better understand the deep structures of the concepts and will be better at transfer with invent-and-tell method. Inventing with contrasting cases also helps recall and contextualize", "Question_id": 5, "Student_score_on_question": 0.5, "Student_choice_on_question": "A,B,C,D", "Quiz_score": 9.0, "Average_quizzes_score": 7.0}, {"Answer_text": "This type of invent then tell method will promote transfer to other domains and distance transfer over a longer time for students.", "Question_id": 5, "Student_score_on_question": 0.5, "Student_choice_on_question": "C,D", "Quiz_score": 7.0, "Average_quizzes_score": 8.2}, {"Answer_text": "far transfer will be enhanced, deep understanding will be better. However, purely applying formula and tasks mainly involving retentiveness will not be affected.", "Question_id": 5, "Student_score_on_question": 0.5, "Student_choice_on_question": "B,D", "Quiz_score": 6.75, "Average_quizzes_score": 6.7}, {"Answer_text": "Benefits of this methods are (1) delayed recall, students remember the information better for longer and will be able to computer areas for longer (2) pressure transfer task/contextualizing knowledge, more students will use the right formula for area problems after the activity.", "Question_id": 5, "Student_score_on_question": 1.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "A,C", "Quiz_score": 9.0, "Average_quizzes_score": 7.0}, {"Answer_text": "Contrasting cases are helpful for convergent thinking, which leads to come to one correct answer. Invent-with-contrasting-cases (ICC) helps with delayed recall and also helps with contextualize, which can make learners pay more attention to those deeper structures of the problem and is also beneficial to transfer learning.", "Question_id": 5, "Student_score_on_question": 0.5, "Student_choice_on_question": "A,B,C,D", "Quiz_score": 8.0, "Average_quizzes_score": 6.7}, {"Answer_text": "Students will perceive a better learning of the surface area concept", "Question_id": 5, "Student_score_on_question": 0.75, "Student_choice_on_question": "A,B,C", "Quiz_score": 7.5, "Average_quizzes_score": 6.8}, {"Answer_text": "According to research findings, students will understand the deep features better, thus be better at selecting the right formula for the problem. They will perform better in late transfer tasks.", "Question_id": 5, "Student_score_on_question": 0.75, "Student_choice_on_question": "A,B,C", "Quiz_score": 8.25, "Average_quizzes_score": 7.3}, {"Answer_text": "Students would get deeper knowledge of how areas are computed. By inventing, deep structures will have longer retention. Through contrasting cases some contextualization will occur and help similarities become apparent, reinforcing the deep structures invented.", "Question_id": 5, "Student_score_on_question": 0.5, "Student_choice_on_question": "B,C", "Quiz_score": 8.25, "Average_quizzes_score": 6.8}, {"Answer_text": "Contrasting cases can facilitate sense making by indicating key features of the domain's deep structure by highlighting key similarities and differences. This means students are more likely to understand how the formulas relate to the answers they produce, and thereby students may be more deft in their applications, and better able to recall the formulas in the future. I am unsure what \"perceive a better learning\" means. Is this about their metacognitive awareness/perception of their own learning? I.E. they will 'feel' that they learned more?", "Question_id": 5, "Student_score_on_question": 1.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "A,C", "Quiz_score": 7.0, "Average_quizzes_score": 7.5}, {"Answer_text": "This is an ICC/invent-then-tell instruction. The benefits of doing so always result in better far-transfer and deep understanding and a longer time of recall. Among the options, 'students will perceive better learning of the surface area concept' is correct since it means a deeper understanding of conceptual knowledge.", "Question_id": 5, "Student_score_on_question": 0.5, "Student_choice_on_question": "B,C", "Quiz_score": 9.0, "Average_quizzes_score": 8.3}, {"Answer_text": "They create and test their own hypothesis, which helps with far-transfer.", "Question_id": 5, "Student_score_on_question": 0.25, "Student_choice_on_question": "B", "Quiz_score": 8.0, "Average_quizzes_score": 8.0}, {"Answer_text": "Given that there are many parameters to be considered here, I would test both design patterns against each other in a constrained environment. If the resources were not available to conduct testing in such a manner, I would choose the max-welfare design pattern because it has greater flexibility that the stable pattern, if it doesn't work well I would switch.", "Question_id": 6, "Student_score_on_question": 1.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "A", "Quiz_score": 8.0, "Average_quizzes_score": 8.2}, {"Answer_text": "I will conduct an experiment to see how the different patterns bring me to and then decide.", "Question_id": 6, "Student_score_on_question": 1.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "A", "Quiz_score": 7.75, "Average_quizzes_score": 7.6}, {"Answer_text": "Since the max welfare design pattern suggests that learners be paired for peer-tutoring over multiple sessions so that they gain the maximum from each other in that session, it would be more optimal.", "Question_id": 6, "Student_score_on_question": 0.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "C", "Quiz_score": 6.75, "Average_quizzes_score": 6.4}, {"Answer_text": "Max-welfare. Because mobile app makes it easier to communicate with different people anytime and anywhere. It also costs less to find a new teammate. It can also use computer-determined methods to find the best pairing.", "Question_id": 6, "Student_score_on_question": 0.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "C", "Quiz_score": 6.75, "Average_quizzes_score": 7.6}, {"Answer_text": "Conduct a controlled test (or A/B test) to see which pattern yields the best result in our app.", "Question_id": 6, "Student_score_on_question": 1.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "A", "Quiz_score": 8.75, "Average_quizzes_score": 6.8}, {"Answer_text": "Choose the max-welfare pattern because max-welfare would choose the stable-matching pairing if that were indeed more optimal\u3002", "Question_id": 6, "Student_score_on_question": 0.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "C", "Quiz_score": 9.0, "Average_quizzes_score": 8.3}, {"Answer_text": "Since the app allows learners to participate in tutoring over any duration, Max-welfare would be more flexible.", "Question_id": 6, "Student_score_on_question": 0.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "C", "Quiz_score": 7.75, "Average_quizzes_score": 7.0}, {"Answer_text": "Since we are in online media, I would pick max-welfare. The reason is that if learners are not required to come to the same classroom by the same time, then it is very hard to ensure that learners in single pair are able to synchronise. Given that online media often assumes self-paced learning it might also be an issue (i.e. I decide to take vacation and my partner should wait till I return). In contrast, max-welfare makes decision for each session and can pick partner from those who are currently online which is very convenient.", "Question_id": 6, "Student_score_on_question": 1.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "A", "Quiz_score": 9.75, "Average_quizzes_score": 8.1}, {"Answer_text": "A/B testing to compare the two design patterns", "Question_id": 6, "Student_score_on_question": 1.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "A", "Quiz_score": 10.0, "Average_quizzes_score": 6.7}, {"Answer_text": "Max-welfare, because people are flowing fast, you cannot tell who will still be here tomorrow, so it's hard to form stable patterns. Rather, pair people with max gain will be more beneficial.", "Question_id": 6, "Student_score_on_question": 0.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "C", "Quiz_score": 7.0, "Average_quizzes_score": 8.0}, {"Answer_text": "I might begin with a single question that asks users, given a particular tutoring topic, how long they plan to participate with options of 1) once, 2) less than a month, 3) a month or more. Then I would choose max welfare for options 1 and 2 and stable pairing for option 3. If the option 1 or 2 users began to stay with the app longer, it would switch them to stable pairing.", "Question_id": 6, "Student_score_on_question": 1.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "A", "Quiz_score": 8.0, "Average_quizzes_score": 8.1}, {"Answer_text": "We may need further experimental data to decide, so an A/B test is good.", "Question_id": 6, "Student_score_on_question": 1.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "A", "Quiz_score": 8.75, "Average_quizzes_score": 6.7}, {"Answer_text": "Since design patterns don't provide a principle to guide us choosing better practices, I suggest trying the easier pattern to implement first (e.g. stable-pairing), then move to max-welfare if results are inadequate", "Question_id": 6, "Student_score_on_question": 0.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "B", "Quiz_score": 7.0, "Average_quizzes_score": 7.3}, {"Answer_text": "As both these design patterns have certain learning benefits, I would decide to use Max-welfare because it allows students to choose whether they want to be paired with the same person or not. If they want to be paired with the same person, then they are actually using the stable-pairing design pattern.", "Question_id": 6, "Student_score_on_question": 0.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "C", "Quiz_score": 8.0, "Average_quizzes_score": 6.9}, {"Answer_text": "If we want the learner to have the max learning gain, then it's better to use \"Max-welfare\" because learners can experience diverse experience and empathy.", "Question_id": 6, "Student_score_on_question": 0.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "C", "Quiz_score": 7.0, "Average_quizzes_score": 7.8}, {"Answer_text": "Assuming these patterns are fairly simple to implement, you could implement both and A/B test them to see which is producing better outcomes or maintaining users better. Opt for the solution fulfilling those metrics better.", "Question_id": 6, "Student_score_on_question": 1.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "A", "Quiz_score": 5.75, "Average_quizzes_score": 6.8}, {"Answer_text": "Stable pairing can detract from diversity in learning. As such, it is better to opt for the max welfare pattern.", "Question_id": 6, "Student_score_on_question": 0.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "C", "Quiz_score": 6.75, "Average_quizzes_score": 7.1}, {"Answer_text": "I would choose a design pattern that could yield the most gains for learners over the course of their study. Max-welfare design pattern seems to be most aligned with this goal. But most practically, I would suggest moving with stable-pairing first.", "Question_id": 6, "Student_score_on_question": 0.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "B", "Quiz_score": 8.75, "Average_quizzes_score": 6.8}, {"Answer_text": "One option could be to differentiate the pairing algorithm based on the time frame for the use case. So if a given user signals that they need only a few sessions, we could use Max-Welfare, but if they will be going back again and again, we use Stable-Pairing", "Question_id": 6, "Student_score_on_question": 1.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "A", "Quiz_score": 8.5, "Average_quizzes_score": 7.5}, {"Answer_text": "I would analyze which design pattern matches users' needs when using a smartphone, using properties that are unique to a smartphone environment. One characteristic that the digital tool has is using algorithm to make proper pairs. For that reason, I would choose to use the \"Max-welfare\" pattern over the \"stable-pairing\" pattern.", "Question_id": 6, "Student_score_on_question": 0.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "C", "Quiz_score": 8.0, "Average_quizzes_score": 7.3}, {"Answer_text": "Test both to see which one works better because there is no adequate/standard way of comparing two solutions and deciding which one is better. Better to be sure than utilize a less optimal method.", "Question_id": 6, "Student_score_on_question": 1.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "A", "Quiz_score": 7.5, "Average_quizzes_score": 7.0}, {"Answer_text": "The best way is to test both patterns and compare them with each other through AB testing.", "Question_id": 6, "Student_score_on_question": 1.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "A", "Quiz_score": 8.0, "Average_quizzes_score": 7.2}, {"Answer_text": "Since these two are competing solutions, I think the designer should make two prototypes to test the result and see which fits the learning goal better.", "Question_id": 6, "Student_score_on_question": 1.0, "Student_choice_on_question": "A", "Quiz_score": 7.75, "Average_quizzes_score": 7.7}]